Guide to the Harry Shulman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- SUBJECT FILES, 1922-1955; Series III; 4 linear feet (9 boxes)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 265)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 266)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, civil procedure, undated (Box 18, Folder 267)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, constitutional law, undated (Box 18, Folder 268)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, contracts, undated (Box 18, Folder 269)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, evidence, undated (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, jurisprudence, 1926-1927 (Box 19, Folder 271)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, legal liability, undated (Box 19, Folder 272)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, property, undated (Box 19, Folder 273)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, Roman law, undated (Box 20, Folder 274-245)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, sales, undated (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, torts, undated (Box 20, Folder 277)
  - Shulman, Harry: law school notes, trusts, undated (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Shulman, Harry: Holmes lecture, (1955) (Box 21, Folder 279-280)
  - Shulman, Harry: lecture notes, (1930) (Box 21, Folder 281)
  - Shulman, Harry: life insurance, 1937-1938, undated (Box 21, Folder 282)
  - Shulman, Harry: miscellaneous, undated (Box 21, Folder 283)
  - Shulman, Harry: notes, etc. on public control of business, 1933-1937 (Box 21, Folder 284-288)
  - Shulman, Harry: research notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 289-291)
  - Shulman, Harry: speeches, undated (Box 22, Folder 292)
  - Smith, Nellie Van D., Human Relations Labor and Management, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 293)
  - Steel industry dispute, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 294)
  - Student paper: "The Closed Shop-- shall We Revive It?" by George Bennett, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 295)
  - Student paper: "Freedom of Speech and the Employer" by George Bennett, undated (Box 22, Folder 296)
  - Student paper: "Jurisdictional Disputes" by David E. Rice, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 297)
  - Student paper: "Labor-Management Legislation in the Philippines" by Gonzalo M. Gonzales, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 298)
  - Student paper: "Labor Relations" by William R. Shuttleworth, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 299)
  - Student paper: "Paternalism--A Lingering Fallacy" by Howard M.Holtzman, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 300)
  - Student paper: "Seniority Clauses in Collective Bargaining Agreements" by Russ Karp, undated (Box 22, Folder 301)
  - "Survey Supreme Court October Term 1929", (1929-1930) (Box 22, Folder 302)
  - Yale School of Law: Program of Research in the Administration of Law, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 303)
  - Yale University: Committee on Personnel Policy, 1945-1947, n.d (Box 22, Folder 304)
- WRITINGS, 1934-1953; Series IV; 0.75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  Box 23 of WRITINGS contains published books and articles written or reviewed by Harry Shulman. Box 24 has manuscripts and drafts of additional writings by Shulman. The material in each box is arranged alphabetically.
  - "The Case For and Against the Constitutionality of the Social Security Act", 1936 (Box 23, Folder 305)
  - "The Case for the Constitutionality of the Social Security Act", 1936 (Box 23, Folder 306)
  - Conference: Less Government in Labor-Management Relations: An Achievable Goal?, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 307)
  - Industrial Discipline and the Arbitration Process, book review by Harry Shulman, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 308)
  - Jury Trial in Civil Cases--A Study in Judicial Administration by Charles E. Clark and Harry Shulman, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 309)
  - "Mortgage Foreclosures in Superior Court for New Haven County, at New Haven, 1929-1932" by Harry Shulman and Richard Thompson, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 310)
  - Opinions of the Umpire, 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 311)
  - "The Role of Arbitration in the Collective Bargaining Process", 1949 (Box 23, Folder 312)
  - "The Settlement of Labor Disputes", 1949 (Box 23, Folder 313)
  - "Some Jurisdictional Limitations on Federal Procedure" by Harry Shulman and Edward C. Jaegerman, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 314)
  - Supreme Court reply brief: Railroad Retirement Board et al v. The Atton, Railroad Company et al, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - Manuscript: chapter on American Labor law, undated (Box 24, Folder 316)
  - Manuscript: chapter on "Judicial Review", 1940 (Box 24, Folder 317-318)
  - Manuscript: chapter on "Labor Disputes", undated (Box 24, Folder 319-321)
  - Manuscript: chapter on liability in a strike, undated (Box 24, Folder 322)
  - Manuscript: chapter on "Medieval Law and Society", undated (Box 24, Folder 323)
  - Manuscript: chapter on "The Nature and Functions of Law", undated (Box 24, Folder 324)
  - Manuscript: chapter on "Unemployment", undated (Box 24, Folder 325-326)
  - Manuscript: "Teaching Civil Liberties in the Law School" by Harry Shulman and Herbert A Fierst, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 327)
  - Miscellaneous corrections, undated (Box 24, Folder 328)
  - Notes, etc. on the public control of business, 1934-1939 (Box 24, Folder 329)